salefinder.co.nz 2019-02-28

# Online Retail Specials Catalogues - Sale Finder

**SaleFinder Privacy Policy**

This is the Privacy Policy for www.salefinder.co.nz ("the Website"). This Privacy Policy relates to the collection and use of your personal information that you may supply to SaleFinder Limited ("we", "us" and "our") through your use of the Website.

At SaleFinder, we are committed to ensuring the privacy of our clients and our users. This Privacy Policy describes how use the information we collect when you visit our website and/or register to receive our email sale alerts and weekly newsletters.

**Types of personal information collected by SaleFinder**   
So we can give you customised information about all the latest catalogues, sales and other promotions from your favourite retailers, we will ask you for the following information:

  * Name; 
  * your email address; and 
  * the region you live in

Because we value your membership to the Website, we will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent.

We will also from time to time ask you for further information so we can tailor the content of the Website to make your experience of SaleFinder even more valuable to you. You may voluntarily provide further demographic information such as your age, favourite retailers and other buying preferences. We may ask for your mobile phone number if you wish to receive SMS message alerts. If presented to our clients, this information will always remain in an aggregated, anonymous form. This means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.

**Usage of Information collected by SaleFinder**   
In addition to collecting personal and non-personal information, SaleFinder may also collect non-personal, aggregated information about members' use of the Website. This information is not personally identifiable and will only be used to find out how members use our service and site. For example, this information will tell us how much time users spend on our site, from which other sites members came, and to what other sites members go. The collection of this information allows us to, among other things, prepare for traffic load demands and to deliver email sale alerts and newsletters to you efficiently.

**Disclosure of Information collected by SaleFinder**   
SaleFinder will share your personal information with other companies or individuals in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
  * We provide such information to our affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.

We may share with third parties (without notice to you) certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular promotion. Such information does not identify you individually in any way.

**Review and Access**   
Upon your request, we will provide you with a summary of the information we collect about you. You will have an opportunity to correct, update or modify this information.

**Unsubscribe**   
If we ever send you information by e-mail concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an e-mail address by which you may request no future notices from that email. Please use the link provided on the email to unsubscribe from the relevant service.

**Cookies**   
Commonly used by most websites, Cookies are data that the Website transfers to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can facilitate your ongoing access to and use of the Website. They allow us to customise the Website to your needs, such as welcoming you back to the Website and remembering your preferences, such your selected region within New Zealand. If you do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, you can set your browser to disable acceptance of cookies. However, doing so will reduce the ability of SaleFinder to provide its full range of services. It is recommended that you set your computer to allow our Cookies. Cookies do not provide SaleFinder with any personally identifiable information.

**Links to Other Sites**   
As part of the service, SaleFinder may create links allowing you to access third party websites such as member retailer websites. SaleFinder is not responsible for the content that appears on these sites and does not necessarily endorse these sites. Please consult those websites' individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

**Security**   
All information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

**Modification to this Policy**   
SaleFinder may from time to time modify and/or update this policy. Any changes will be posted on this Privacy Policy page.

**Contact Us**   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the SaleFinder website in general, please contact us at admin@salefinder.co.nz
